<resources>

    <string-array name='tipsArray'>
        <item>Tap the red \'?\' in the upper left of any screen for detailed information and help.</item>
        <item>The tutorial can be replayed from the Settings menu if you need a reminder.</item>
        <item>Game sounds / music can be turned off in the Settings, along with notification sounds.</item>
        <item>All notifications (Market Restock, Visitor Spawn, Worker Return, Bonus Chest Refill) can be enabled / disabled in the Settings menu.</item>
        <item>A Visitor\'s Required Trades are listed in black.</item>
        <item>A Visitor\'s Optional Trades are listed in grey.</item>
        <item>Completing all of a Visitor\'s Required and Optional Trades will earn you a doubled gift from the satisfied customer.</item>
        <item>Try to combine a Visitor\'s Preferences to earn the most Coins.</item>
        <item>Can\'t complete all of a Visitor\'s Required Trades? It may be best to just Dismiss them via the \'X\' button and move on.</item>
        <item>Reduce the cost of Dismissing a Visitor by completing as many Optional and Required Trades as you can.</item>
        <item>Not sure if that is Iron or Steel that a Visitor prefers? Tap on a Visitor\'s discovered Preference to see a description of it.</item>
        <item>Want a new Visitor? Get one immediately by using the grey and white button with a plus sign to either pay Coins or watch a brief advertisement.</item>
        <item>Need some quick coins? You can sell excess items from your Inventory as a last resort, but any bonus coin upgrades won\'t apply!</item>
        <item>Unfinished items are marked with "(unf)" at the beginning of their name. These sell for half as much as finished items and may cause you to lose money.</item>
        <item>As your level increases, new Traders will arrive at the Market. You can unlock up to 56 different Traders, with new ones being added regularly.</item>
        <item>Some Traders have additional stock that you can unlock as you purchase items. The more you buy from them, the more you unlock.</item>
        <item>After you\'ve purchased items from a Trader, you can restock that Trader\'s items by using the Restock button and paying coins or watching a brief advertisement.</item>
        <item>Once you\'ve purchased all items a Trader currently has available, the Trader will leave when the window is closed. Then, a new Trader will take their place, if there are any more available with stock.</item>
        <item>Bought all the items in the Market? It will Restock automatically after a while. If don\'t want to wait, you can use the Restock All button and pay Coins or watch a brief advertisement for an instant restock.</item>
        <item>Join us at www.reddit.com/r/PixelBlacksmith for gameplay tips, release notes, and all kinds of discussion!</item>
        <item>Want to get in touch on Reddit, Facebook, or Twitter? Look for the "Social Media" section in the Settings menu!</item>
        <item>Found a bug? Submit it at www.reddit.com/r/PixelBlacksmith and it\'ll get fixed!</item>
        <item>Pages can be found by completing quests, achieving visitor trophies, sending out workers with food, and opening the bonus chest.</item>
        <item>Premium players can disable all adverts from the settings menu.</item>
        <item>Premium players can prestige their account multiple times and enter New Game+ mode via the Settings menu.</item>
        <item>A log of the last 100 important messages can be viewed in the Settings menu.</item>
        <item>The game\'s credits can be viewed in the Settings menu.</item>
        <item>Received a support code from customer support? Enter it in the Settings menu.</item>
        <item>Want to see all your Google Play achievements / leaderboard? Head to the Settings menu.</item>
        <item>Getting a snazzy new phone? Make sure to cloud save via the Settings menu first!</item>
        <item>As your level increases, new Traders will arrive at the Market. You can unlock up to 56 different Traders, with new ones being added regularly.</item>
        <item>Some Traders have additional stock that you can unlock as you purchase items. The more you buy from them, the more you unlock.</item>
        <item>After you\'ve purchased items from a Trader, you can restock that Trader\'s items by using the Restock button and paying coins or watching a brief advertisement.</item>
        <item>Once you\'ve purchased all items a Trader currently has available, the Trader will leave when the window is closed. Then, a new Trader will take their place, if there are any more available with stock.</item>
        <item>Bought all the items in the Market? It will Restock automatically after a while. If don\'t want to wait, you can use the Restock All button and pay Coins or watch a brief advertisement for an instant restock.</item>
        <item>An extra Visitor automatically shows up every 25 minutes. This can be decreased to only 10 minutes by upgrading "Visitor Spawn Time".</item>
        <item>The Market restocks automatically every 24 hours. This can be reduced to only 2 hours by upgrading "Market Restock Time".</item>
        <item>Initially, you can only have up to 2 Visitors at the same time. This can be increased to 10 Visitors by upgrading "Maximum Visitors".</item>
        <item>The Market starts with 3 Traders displayed at the same time. This can be raised to 10 Traders by upgrading "Maximum Traders".</item>
        <item>The "Coins Bonus" upgrade gives extra Coins on every single Visitor Trade you complete. This upgrade is extremely powerful and should not be overlooked!</item>
        <item>Interested in levelling faster? The "XP Bonus" upgrade increases all experience you earn.</item>
        <item>Are the high Tier items taking too long to craft? Investing in "Craft Time" upgrades can help.</item>
        <item>The "Craft Time" upgrade also reduces the time it takes for items purchased at the Market to be delivered, and the time it takes to sell items from your Inventory.</item>
        <item>Helpers and heroes initially take 3 hours to return with resources. This can be reduced to just 30 minutes by upgrading "Worker Time".</item>
        <item>Completing a Visitor\'s Required Trades earns a gift of 1 to 5 random items. This can be increased up to 5 to 15 items by upgrading "Visitor Rewards".</item>
        <item>Receive up to 30 items as a gift from a satisfied Visitor by maxing the "Visitor Rewards" upgrade and completing all Required and Optional Trades.</item>
        <item>There are 7 different hirable Helpers that unlock as you level up.</item>
        <item>You only have to pay to hire each different Helper once. After you\'ve hired a Helper, they will continue to work for you as long as you want to give them a job to do.</item>
        <item>Helpers need Tools. You can either craft Tools or buy them from the Market.</item>
        <item>Are all your workers using their favourite food? Turn on autofeed to keep them topped up automatically!</item>
        <item>There are 8 different types of Tools that Helpers can use: Pickaxes, Hammers, Fishing Rods, Hatchets, Gloves, Gems, Rings, and Visages.</item>
        <item>A Helper with a Pickaxe, Hammer, or Ring will gather materials worth more Coins than the other Tools. But sometimes you really need the materials the other Tools provide.</item>
        <item>Equipping a Helper with a better Tool will produce better results. Craft or buy higher Tier Tools to get higher Tier materials.</item>
        <item>Once you\'ve equipped a Helper with a Tool, you can press the display to the right of the Tool to get a list of how many items they will gather.</item>
        <item>Everyone does a better job when they aren\'t hungry! Your Workers included. Give your Helper a Food item to increase how much they will gather.</item>
        <item>The Foods that you craft may provide a higher Helper gather bonus than the Foods you can buy in the Market.</item>
        <item>Each Helper has a different secret Food that they prefer and that provides a double gather bonus. Once you\'ve discovered their preferred Food, the gather bonus will be displayed in a green color.</item>
        <item>Providing your Helpers with Food gives a small chance that they will bring back a special Page item. Using their preferred Food increases this chance.</item>
        <item>Heroes are a riskier way to earn items, but can be very profitable!</item>
        <item>Make the most of a hero\'s item preferences to complete the trickier quests.</item>
        <item>The worker notification will inform you when both heroes and helpers have returned.</item>
        <item>When pressed, messages can either show the message log, or disappear. Change it in the settings!</item>
        <item>Fullscreen mode provides a more immersive mode, but can drain battery faster!</item>
        <item>If you\'re experiencing performance issues, try turning off auto-refresh in the settings!</item>
        <item>Messages disappearing too quickly? Enable longer messages in the settings.</item>
        <item>Hero quests can be more rewarding, but there\'s a chance of losing items.</item>
        <item>Pay attention to hero preferences, they make a massive difference to hero effectiveness!</item>
        <item>Contributors can unlock beta access, suggest new items / quests / visitors, and more, via the premium screen.</item>
        <item>Traders can be locked in place for a price. Once locked, they\'ll charge higher prices but restock for free!</item>
        <item>Want to leave the game until your items have finished crafting / selling / buying? Make sure the notification is turned on!</item>
        <item>Having trouble reaching 100%% completion? Tap your completion %% to see a breakdown of your progress.</item>
        <item>The game can be locked in portrait or landscape if you prefer playing a certain way.</item>
        <item>Enchanted items will have a coloured tint to them, to help easily identify them.</item>
        <item>Long press an item to lock it, making it unsellable and untradeable. Useful when saving items for a worker or hero!</item>
        <item>The sheets on the table below the shop visitors can be tapped to quickly access the message log.</item>
        <item>Running low on coins? Packs can be bought by tapping the plus button next to your coin count. The higher your level, the more coins you\'ll get!</item>
        <item>Large quantities of item can be crafted in a single stack. This lets other items be crafted at the same time as a large order.</item>
        <item>Once a visitor\'s trophy has been earned, the spawn chance is cut in half.</item>
        <item>Heroes can \'super succeed\' if on an easy adventure, earning 1.1 to 2.5x the usual reward.</item>
        <item>Heroes can be made more powerful for free by making use of sets, unique combinations of items that boost hero strength.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>